{
    "subject": "resource/Britannia_Industries",
    "predicate": "property/intl",
    "object": "yes",
    "human_readable": "Britannia Industries operates internationally.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9467637538909912,
            "question": "Are there any challenges associated with operating internationally for Britannia Industries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9457975029945374,
            "question": "What is the scope of Britannia Industries' operations globally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9170216917991638,
            "question": "What are the advantages of Britannia Industries operating internationally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8475967049598694,
            "question": "Has Britannia Industries faced any cultural or regulatory differences in its international operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8166847825050354,
            "question": "How does Britannia Industries' international presence impact its business?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8000686764717102,
            "question": "In what countries does Britannia Industries have a presence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7543871402740479,
            "question": "How does Britannia Industries adapt its products and marketing strategies to different international markets?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7255748510360718,
            "question": "What products are primarily associated with Britannia Industries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7172286510467529,
            "question": "What are the future prospects for Britannia Industries' international expansion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6526311039924622,
            "question": "Does Britannia Industries operate solely within India?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Britannia Industries operates internationally.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1225_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the future prospects for Britannia Industries' international expansion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1225_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What products are primarily associated with Britannia Industries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1225_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Britannia Industries adapt its products and marketing strategies to different international markets?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1225_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1225_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  I can do that as long as they relate to the provided text."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can provide an answer in the form of a structured JSON format.\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention several instances where Britannia Industries is mentioned as operating internationally:\n\n* \"Several of our bakery and dairy brands are available in approximately 30 countries.\" (document 26)\n* The company has acquired stakes in companies based in Dubai, Oman, and plans to expand into new geographies. (document 82)\n* Britannia's products have a global presence and are exported to countries worldwide. (document 58)\n\nThese statements support the triple that Britannia Industries operates internationally."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Britannia Industries expanding its business internationally, mentioning specific international markets and acquisitions. Therefore, the statement that Britannia Industries operates internationally is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}